Guide to the Dorothy Schefer Faux fashion collection, 1931-2017.
Faux, Dorothy Schefer fashion collection
- Fashion publications
  - Visionaire, 1993-2005
    - Visionaire #41, World, 2003; VIS 24 (Box 15)
      Includes designs by Craig McDean, Solve Sundsbo, Abbas, Andreas Angelidakis, Julian Roder, Hiroji Kubota, Salim Langatta, Massimo Vitali, Daniel Klajmic, Leopoldo Gout, Roger Deckker, Hiro, Sebastiaan Bremer, David Sims, Karl Lagerfeld, Steven Meisel, Steven Klein, Mario Testino, Aneta Greszykowska & Jan Smaga, Nan Goldin, Evelyn H. Lauder, Hedi Slimane, Pascal Dangin, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Clementine Van Lamsweerde, Sandra Jonas Bacchi, Sarah Krantman, David Byrne, Vicky Donner, Armin Linke, Scott Lightner, Justin Kaswan, Horst Diekgerdes, Fabio Mergulhao, K.T. Kim, Dan Harris, Enrique Badulescu, Peter Lindbergh, Tobias Schweitzer, Mats Gustafson, Raf Simons, Bert Houbrecht, Anthony Gormley, Mario Sorrenti, Brigitte Grignet, Thomas Nutzl, Frederic Lagrange, Patrick Demarchelier, Dimitrios Georges Antonitsis, Jeremie Rozan, Roman Rozan, Pratima Naithani, Priya Ray, Gustavo Di Mario, Christiano, Tony Cox, Noah Shelley, Nabil Gholam, Ricardo Cruz, Jake McCabe, Embry Rucker, Daniel Joseph, Ramona Stacconia, Sally Penn, Roman Alonso, Matthew Hranek, Jean Roman Seyfried, Hellin Kay, Francois Berthoud, Lisa Eisner, Sergio Bartelsman, Neil Lucente & Claudine Sia, Ricardo Alzati, Jim Tolley, Jessica Kemps, Koji Shimizu, Rob Pruitt & Jonathan Horowitz, Collier Schorr, Wing Shya, Alexandre De Betak, Gemma Hart Corsano, Drew Jarrett, Jaime Alvarez, Hillary Launey, Jenny Riffle, Bryce Pincham, Michael Clinton, Taryn Simon, Huw Gwyther, Yaroslav "slava" Mogutin, Trevor Tondro, Lili Holzer-Glier, Jenny Holzer, Sa Schloff, Joanne Murphy, Hisashi Murayama, Michael Simon, America Cupello, Tony Wasser, Neale Albert, Yelena Yemchuck, Veronique Branquinho, Liya Kebede, Marisol Villanueva, Enamul Hoque, Kelly Klein, Iman, Sante D'Orazio, Lizzie Leigh Horan, Crawford Morgan, Shoji Van Kuzumi, Richard Burbridge, Regan Cameron, Philip-Lorca Dicorcia, Towa Tei, Patrick Kinmonth, Lauren Krohn, Sarah Small, TOm Sachs, Ari Marcopoulos, Carlos Jose B. Dias Garcia Jr., Sonia P. Mohr, Adam Whitehead, Alexi Lubomirski, Bruno Cals, Arthur Marks, Michal Rubin, Christy Turlington, Elaine Gan, Plamen Petkov, Natasha Papadopoulou, David Armstrong, Giovanna Zaccagnini, Isabel & Ruben Toledo, Domenico Dolce & Stefano Gabbana, Stefano Guindani, Peetssa, Sam Taylor-Wood, Paola Kudaski & Nicolas Malleville, Majed Al-Sabah, Stephane Sednaoui, Jordan Doner, Tatiana Gaz, Ivan Abuljamra, Satoshi Saikusa, Piotr Uklanski, Wanda Acosta, Baz Luhrmann, Darren Almond, Stephen Gan, Jaques Faing, Mikael Jansson, Tessa Traeger, Gap
    - Visionaire #42, Scent, 2003; VIS 25; International Flavors & Fragrances, Inc. (Box 3)
      Includes designs by Mario Sorrenti, Vera Degen & Yves Cassar, Hedi Slimane, Olivier Polge, Philip-Lorca diCorcia, Christophe Laudamiel, Karl Lagerfeld, Sandrine Malin, Craig McDean, Carlos Benaim, Laurent Bruyere & Carlos Benaim, Sam Taylor-Wood, Laurent le Guernec, Mario Testino, David Bowie, Iman, Dan Forbes, Nick Knight, Martine Pallix & Anne Sophie Chapuis, Vanessa Beecroft, Domitille Bertier, Mark Romanek, Jean Marc Chaillan, Kate Moss, Marcus Piggott & Mert Alas, Andreas Gursky, Sophia Grojsman, Stephen King, Pierre Wargnye & Braja Mookherjee, Peter Saville, Pascal Gaurin, Jean-Georges Vongerichten, Richard Burbridge, Loc Dong, Gus Van Sant, Laurent le Guernec, Terry Richardson, Dominique Ropion, Zaha Hadid, Sophie Labbe, Inez van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Bruno Jovanovic, Pascal Dangin, Sophia Grojsman
    - Visionaire #43, Dreams, 2004; VIS 26 (Box 3)
      Includes designs by David Sims, Adam Fuss, Nick Knight, Philip Taaffe, Craig McDean, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Rachel Whiteread, Steven Klein, Roni Horn, Simon Periton, Karl Lagerfeld, Mario Sorrenti, Maurizio Cattelan, Bruce WeberRobert Longo,
    - Visionaire #44, Toys, 2004; VIS 27; Red Set (Box 16)
      Includes designs by Marc Jacobs for Louis Vuitton, Domenico Dolce, Stefano Gabbana, Hedi Slimane, Viktor Horsting, Rold Snoeren, Muccia Prada
    - Visionaire #45, More Toys, 2004; VIS 28; Blue Set (Box 16)
      Includes designs by John Galliano, Helmut Lang, Jean-Paul Gaultier, Stefano Pilati for Yves Saint Laurent, Giorgio Armani
    - Visionaire #46, Uncensored, 2005; VIS 29; Testino, Mario (Box 1)
      Includes designs by Ghada Amer, Nobuyoshi Araki, Norbert Bisky, Robin Broadbent, Elina Brotherus, Cecily Brown, Jeff Burton, Bonnie Camplin, Gillian Carnegie, Leo Chiachio, Catherine Chalmers, Dan Colen, John Currin, Gerald Davis, Wim Delvoye, Amie Dicke, Marlene Dumas, Marcel Dzama, Martin Eder, Judith Eisler, Tracey Emin, Angus Fairhurst, Tom Gallant, Nan Goldin, Christian Holstad, Harmony Korine, Cary Kwok, Debbie Lawson, Jorge Lopez, Sarah Lucas, Ryan McGinley, Dawn Mellor, Yan Pei-Ming, Slava Mogutin, Vik Muniz, Lennart Nilsson, Tim Noble & Sue Webster, Raymond Pettibon, Richard Prince, Tal R., Thomas Ruff, Dean Sameshima, Collier Schorr, Nigel Shafran, Daniel Sinsel, Spencer Sweeney, Sam Taylor-Wood, Simon Thompson, Palle Torsson, Wolfgang Tillmans, Vinogradov & Dubossarsky, Sue Williams, Lisa Yuskavage, Mario Testino
  - Fashion and various other periodicals, 1993-2016
    - View on Colour: L'Atelier, March 1996; View on Colour: The Colour Forecasting Book; United Publishers S. A. (Box 25)
      No. 8
    - View on Colour: Animality, March 1997; View on Colour: The Colour Forecasting Book; United Publishers S. A. (Box 25)
      No. 10
    - View on Colour: Knitting, October 1998; View on Colour: The Colour Forecasting Book; United Publishers S. A. (Box 25)
      No. 13
    - Issey Miyake: A View on Colour Special, October 1998; View on Colour: The Colour Forecasting Book; United Publishers S. A. (Box 25)
    - La Mode en Peinture, February 1989 (Box 25)
      No. 14
    - The New York Times Magazine: Fashions of the Times: Fall's Big Stories, Fall 1988; The New York Times (Box 25)
      Part 2
    - Rolling Stone: Women of Rock XXX, November 11-13, 1997; Rolling Stone (Box 25)
      The 30th Anniversary Issue
    - American Photo: Special Model Issue, July-August 1996; American Photo (Box 25)
      Vol. VII, No. 4
    - Blue: A Journal for the New Traveler, October, 15, 1997; Blue Media Ventures LLC (Box 25)
      Premier Issue
    - Le Magazine de Chanel, May 6, 1993; Chanel Inc. (Box 25)
    - The Informationist: Leonard Lauder, Master of the Dream Machine, March 1996; Mottus & Associates LTD. (Box 25)
      Vol. 17, No. 3
    - Vogue: A Century of Style, December 1999; Vogue (Box 25)
      Special Millennium Issue; two copies
    - Plus Eighty One: Creators on the Line, Autumn 1997; D. D. Wave Co., LTD. (Box 25)
      Vol. 1
    - Ralph Lauren, Fall 2013 (Box 25)
      Issue IV
    - Ralph Lauren, Spring 2015 (Box 25)
      Issue VII
    - Worth Avenue, 1999 (Box 25)
    - 31 Rue Cambon: Chanel Magazine, Spring-Summer 2015; Chanel (Box 25)
      Issue 11
    - Vogue Italia: Edizioni Condé Nast, May 1989; Vogue (Box 25)
      No. 469
    - W: 2000 Maniacs, March 1999; W (Box 26)
    - Andy Warhol's Interview, February 1996; Brant Publications, Inc. (Box 26)
    - Vogue's Index, 1996; Vogue (Box 26)
    - Vogue: 75 Years, 1916-1991, 1991; Vogue (Box 26)
    - Donna: Gente Vera, November 1993; Donna (Box 26)
      No. 11
    - Dior: Collection Printemps-Été 1996, 1996; Christian Dior (Box 26)
    - Chanel Magazine, 1995; Chanel (Box 26)
    - V Magazine: Ah Men!, September-October 1999; V Magazine (Box 27)
      First issue
    - 31 Rue Cambon: Chanel Magazine, Fall-Winter 2011; Chanel (Box 27)
    - Le Monde d'Hermès, Autumn-Winter 2016; Hermès Paris (Box 27)
      Number 69
    - The Art of Fashion: Financial Times Weekend, Autumn-Winter 2016; Financial Times (Box 27)
    - Fashions of the Times, November 2, 1947; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, September 9, 1951; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 2, 1952; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 30, 1952; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, September 13, 1953; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, February 20, 1955; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, February 12, 1956; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, May 6, 1956; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, November 11, 1956; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 17, 1957; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, May 5, 1957; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March, 2, 1958; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 1, 1959; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 6, 1960; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 6, 1960; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 20, 1960; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, February 26, 1961; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 27, 1961; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 4, 1962; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 25, 1963; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, February 23, 1964; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 30, 1964; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 7, 1965; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 22, 1965; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, January 9, 1966; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, February 26, 1967; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 25, 1968; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 2, 1969; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 24, 1969; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 4, 1979; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, March 7, 1982; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 29, 1982; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 24, 1986; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Fashions of the Times, August 20, 1989; New York Times Magazine (Box 31)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 27, 1953; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, May 1, 1955; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 23, 1956; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 28, 1957; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 27, 1958; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 28, 1958; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 26, 1959; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 27, 1959; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 24, 1960; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 11, 1960; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 23, 1961; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 17, 1961; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 29, 1962; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 16, 1962; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 26, 1964; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 1, 1964; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 25, 1965; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 19, 1965; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 18, 1966; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 1967; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 17, 1967; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 21, 1968; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 15, 1968; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, April 1969; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 14, 1960; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Report on Men's Wear, September 11, 1983; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, August 11, 1963; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, March 14, 1965; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, August 15, 1965; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, March 13, 1966; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, March 12, 1967; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, March 17, 1968; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, March 16, 1969; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Children's Fashions, August 10, 1969; New York Times Magazine (Box 32)
    - Dressmaking at Home, October 1908 (Box 33)
    - The Designer and The Woman' Magazine, July 1925 (Box 33)
    - The Tatler, August 12, 1931 (Box 33)
    - Style, November 1932; American-Mitchell Style Corporation (Box 33)
    - The Sphere, November 8, 1957 (Box 33)
    - The Sphere, November 14, 1958 (Box 33)
    - The Sphere, November 11, 1960 (Box 33)
    - Apollo, May 1966 (Box 33)
    - McCall;s Children's Wear, January-March 1966 (Box 33)
    - Antiques, October 1944 (Box 33)
    - Holly Leaves, 1961 (Box 33)
    - Holly Leaves, 1963 (Box 33)
    - Holiday, the Book of New York, 1949; Curtis Publishing (Box 33)
    - Neue Mode, October 1969 (Box 33)
    - Brigitte, August 20, 1963 (Box 33)
    - Holly Leaves, 1963 (Box 33)
    - Burda, December 1963 (Box 33)
      In German
    - Burda, October 1965 (Box 33)
    - Burda, January 1968 (Box 33)
    - Burda, December 1963 (Box 33)
    - The Sketch, July 30, 1952 (Box 33)
    - The Sketch, August 13, 1952 (Box 33)
    - The Sketch, August 27, 1952 (Box 33)
    - Eve's Annual, 1955; Jasmine Mills Limited, Bombay (Box 33)
    - Rundschau, 1978 (Box 33)
    - Silhouette Journal Couture, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Fruits, 2003; Phaidon Press, Tokyo (Box 33)
      In Japanese
    - Fruits, 2004; Phaidon Press, Tokyo (Box 33)
    - Fruits, 2005; Phaidon Press, Tokyo (Box 33)
    - Centurion, Fall 2005; Phaidon Press, Tokoyo (Box 33)
    - Verve, 2006 (Box 33)
    - Ralph Lauren, March 2014 (Box 33)
    - Patek Philippe, the International Magazine, Autumn 2013 (Box 33)
    - Patek Philippe, the International Magazine, Spring 2015 (Box 33)
    - Patek Philippe, the International Magazine, Spring 2016 (Box 33)
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD), 2016; Fairchild Publishing (Box 33)
      Photo issue
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD), 2016; Fairchild Publishing (Box 33)
      WWD honors
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD), April 19, 2017; Farichild Publishing (Box 33)
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD) Special Edition, February 8, 2018; Farichild Publishing (Box 34)
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD) Special Edition, February 9, 2018; Farichild Publishing (Box 34)
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD) Special Edition, February 12, 2018; Farichild Publishing (Box 34)
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD) Special Edition, February 13, 2018; Farichild Publishing (Box 34)
    - Women's Wear Daily (WWD) Special Edition, February 14, 2018; Farichild Publishing (Box 34)
    - Patek Philippe, Autumn 2013 (Box 33)
    - Patek Philippe, Spring 2015 (Box 33)
    - The World of Hermes, 2017 (Box 33)
    - The Art of Fashion, Undated; Financial Times Weekend (Box 33)
      Jewellery special
- Promotional materials and fashion show invitations, 1993-2016
  - Promotional material, 1993-2005
    Includes catalogs, postcards and other mass mailings.
    - Mirabella Magazine, Undated; PROM 1 (Box 19)
    - Council of Fashion Designers of America Awards, 1994; PROM 2 (Box 19)
    - Prada-Men and Women Shoes and Accessories, Fall-Winter 2000; PROM 3a-b (Box 19)
    - Barney's-Manswear, 1996-1997; PROM 4 (Box 19)
    - Nike- Women, Undated; PROM 5 (Box 19)
    - Chanel, Undated; PROM 6 (Box 19)
    - Donna Karen, 1993; PROM 7 (Box 19)
    - Prada, Fall-Winter 2000; PROM 8 (Box 19)
    - Donna Karen (DKNY), 2000; PROM 9 (Box 19)
    - Banana Republic, Undated; PROM 10 (Box 19)
    - Prada, Fall-Winter 2000; PROM 11 (Box 19)
    - Chanel-Perfume, Undated; PROM 12 (Box 19)
    - Chanel, Fall- Winter 1998-1999; PROM 13 (Box 19)
    - Chanel, Spring-Summer 1999; PROM 14 (Box 19)
    - Ralph Lauren, 2005; PROM 15 (Box 19)
    - V Magazine: Gilty as Charged, Fall 2000; PROM 16 (Box 24)
    - Donna Karen-Skin Care, Undated; PROM 17 (Box 19)
    - Cartier, Undated; PROM 18 (Box 19)
    - Rizzoli Universe, Fall 1998; Rizzoli International Publications (Box 25)
    - Fashion Group International: Night of Stars, 1994; Fashion Group International (Box 25)
    - Fashion & Virtue: Textile Patterns and the Print Revolution, 1520-1620, Fall 2015; Speelberg, Femke; Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 25)
    - Jean Patou ma Collection: Parfums D'Epoque, 1925-1964, 1993; Moüy, Jean de (Box 25)
    - Yves Saint Laurent Make-Up Collection, Autumn-Winter 1999-2000; Yves Saint Laurent (Box 25)
    - Helena Rubinstein: Rouge Glorious, Undated; Helena Rubinstein (Box 25)
    - Presentation of the Fall/ Winter 1994 Chanel Ready-to-Wear Collection, June 6, 1994; Chanel (Box 25)
    - Beauty Is Not a Gift It Is a Habit: Germaine Monteil, Undated; Beauty Science, Monteil Paris (Box 25)
    - Eileen Fisher, Spring 2016 (Box 25)
    - History Book, 1992; Lancômia International (Box 25)
    - 7th on Sixth: New York Collections, Fall 1997; 7th on Sixth (Box 25)
    - Aveda, 1997 (Box 25)
    - Prada: Travel, 2011; Prada (Box 25)
    - Prada: Gifts, 2011; Prada (Box 25)
    - Prada: Backpacks, 2015; Prada (Box 25)
    - Prada: Jewels, 2015; Prada (Box 25)
    - Prada: Gifts, 2015; Prada (Box 25)
    - The Louis Cartier Pen, Undated (Box 25)
    - Italia is Love, Undated; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 25)
      Letter; in envelope
    - "Auguri Auguri Auguri da Tutti I Missoni", 2016 (Box 25)
      Holiday greeting card
    - La Grenouille Bastille Day Menu, 2012; La Grenouille (Box 25)
    - Programme for Lou Walters Latin Quarter, Undated; Lou Walters Latin Quarter (Box 25)
    - D. Porthault Catalog, 2000; Porthault, Marc; D. Porthault (Box 25)
    - Chanel: La Nouvelle Constellation, 1995; Chanel (Box 25)
    - Les Parfums Hermès, 1995; Hermès Paris (Box 25)
    - Chanel Joaillerie, Undated; Chanel (Box 25)
    - Kyoteau: Bottled Memories, April 2009; Cheung, Della; Laudamiel, Christophe (Box 25)
      Includes a vial of perfume
    - Manolo Blahnik Promotionals, 1995; Manolo Blahnik (Box 25)
      Seven promotionals and receipt in envelope
    - Chanel Cruise 2010/11, 2010; Chanel (Box 25)
      Empty envelope
    - Three Blank Chanel Greeting Cards, Undated; Chanel (Box 25)
    - Loro Piana Letter, June 2013; Piana, Sergio Loro; Piana, Pier Luigi Loro (Box 25)
    - Two Black Chanel Shopping Bags, Undated; Chanel (Box 25)
    - The New Mademoiselle, 2011; Chanel (Box 25)
      Shopping bag
    - Boucheron Parfums Paris, May 1991; Boucheron Paris (Box 26)
    - Chanel New Products and Promotions: January - June 1998, 1997; Chanel (Box 26)
    - Moda CAD, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Versace Accessories, Spring-Summer 1999; Versace (Box 26)
    - Calvin Klein: Eternity, September 30, 1996; Calvin Klein (Box 26)
    - Ralph Lauren: Romance - Men, Undated; Ralph Lauren (Box 26)
    - Yves Saint Laurent: Champagne Parfum, Undated; Yves Saint Laurent (Box 26)
    - The Bristol-Myers Report: Medicine in the Next Century, March 4, 1987; Bristol-Myers Company; Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (Box 26)
    - The New York Times Magazine: Work: The Great Escape, April 20, 1997; The New York Times (Box 26)
    - Ladies' Compacts of the Nineteenth and Twentieth Centuries, 1989; Gerson, Roselyn; Wallace-Homestead Book Company (Box 26)
    - Yves Saint Laurent: In Love Again, January 24, 1998; Yves Saint Laurent (Box 27)
    - L'un Des Sens, Winter 1989-1990; Chirée, Sylvie de; Hörlin, Birgitt; Editions Assouline (Box 27)
      No. 2; no. 868 of 5000
    - She's Gotta Have It, 1996; Mademoiselle; Condé Nast Publications, Inc. (Box 27)
      Board in paper box with stickers
    - Jimmy Choo, Autumn-Winter 2016 (Box 27)
    - Chanel Fine Jewelry, Undated; Chanel (Box 27)
      Includes two inserts.
    - Manolo Blahnik Fall-Winter Sale Promotion, Undated; Manolo Blahnik (Box 27)
    - Hermès Paris Promotion, Undated; Hermès Paris (Box 27)
    - Cheval d'Orient: A Ceremonial Table, 2008; Hermès Paris (Box 27)
    - Ralph Lauren Collection, Fall 2007; Ralph Lauren (Box 27)
      Includes one insert.
    - Prada: Gifts, 2010; Prada (Box 27)
    - Chanel Cocomaton, Fall-Winter 2011-2012; Chanel (Box 27)
    - Prada Handbags, 2011; Prada (Box 27)
    - Prada Jewels, 2011; Prada (Box 27)
    - Chanel: 2006 Calendar, 2005; Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 27)
    - Volume, 1992 (Box 27)
      Vol. 60
    - Vice Versa, 1999; Yves Saint Laurent (Box 28)
      Includes two CDs
    - Marshall Field's and Christmas, 1981 (Box 33)
    - Marshall Field's and Christmas, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Marshall Field's and Christmas, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Marshall Field's Fall Scenario, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Canada Fashion Mode, Date Unknown (Box 33)
    - Andean Collection, 1967; Jack Lenor Larsen Inc. (Box 33)
    - Shopping Bag, Undated; Warren-Tricomi Salon (Box 33)
    - New Coty, 1999; Coty Inc. (Box 34)
    - Eau De Saint Louis, 1993; Saint Louis (Box 34)
      Includes two slides
    - Cartier Haute Joaillerie Exhbition, 2017; Cartier (Box 34)
    - What' Going On in the Garden of the Hesperides?, 2018; Diptyque (Box 34)
      Includes color chart
  - Fashion show invitations, Date Unknown
    - Fashion Show Invitations-Binder A, Date Unknown; INV 1-38 (Box 20)
    - Fashion Show Invitations-Binder B, Date Unknown; INV 39-84 (Box 21)
- Designer interviews, Fall 1987
  - Binder A, Fall 1987; INT 1-20
    - Designer Interview-Vogue-Vivienne Westwood, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - B. Jackson, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - J. Muir, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Body Map, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Issey Miyake, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Rei Kawakubo, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Matsuda, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Jurgen Lehl, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - R. Lauren, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - C. Klein, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - S. Sprouse, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - N. Kamali, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Basco and Zoran, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - P. Ellis, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - G. Beene, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
  - Binder B, Fall 1987; INT 21-40
    - Valentino, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Missoni, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Babile, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Caumont, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Callaghan, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Basile and Soprani, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Versace, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Ferre, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Biagiotti, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Andre Laug, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Fendi, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Armani, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Complice, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Krizia, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - K. Lagerfeld, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
  - A. Alaia, Fall 1987; INT 41 (Box 21)
  - Givenchy, Fall 1987; INT 42 (Box 21)
  - G.Paulin, Fall 1987; INT 43 (Box 21)
  - G. Penneroux, Fall 1987; INT 44 (Box 21)
  - C. Montana, Fall 1987; INT 45 (Box 21)
  - S, Rykiel, Fall 1987; INT 46 (Box 21)
  - T. Mugler, Fall 1987; INT 47 (Box 21)
- Media, 1967-2001
  - Videos, 1982-2001
    - Revlon Breast Cancer Program 1994, 1994; V-9325 (Box 23)
      VHS
      Old VID 17
    - Fashion Show, Bill Blass Fall 1999 Press Show, Fall 1999; V-9323 (Box 23)
      Old VID 1